abusalehmusakhan@gmail.com M



MD. ABUSALEH MUSA KHAN

KEY SKILLS

- Self-Motivated
- Energetic
- Highly ambitious and agile in nature
- Able to work under challenging condition and long hours
- Able to manage, scheduling a project and have a full organized capacity
- Willing to work in a team organized and dynamic

COMPUTER LITERACY

- ✓ Operating System: Windows 10, Windows 7, Windows Vista, Windows XP.
- ✓ Software Applications: MS Office Suite 2016 (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- ✓ E-mail & Browsing

HOBBIES

- Traveling
- Meeting with new people
- Reading books
- Playing games
- Listening music

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Conversant and proficient both in written and spoken English as well as Bengali.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

I want to work in an organization where experience, skills can make a positive impact in my field of activity leading to Organization growth by creative application of my value based convictions and professional divinity by putting my all efforts in the work assigned.

CAREER SUMMARY

Currently leading Fresh Mart, Paragon Group as Manager (Operation) with the total retails responsibility. Around 8.5+ years experience in Retail Management, Business Launching, Sales Management, Business Strategy, Category Management, HRD & Training Department for Lifestyle and grocery Retail of Bangladesh's largest retail organizations (Fresh Mart, Meena Bazar, Best Buy, Aarong & Kay Kraft). Any kind of retail organization development and retail business starting is my core competency.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

01. Paragon Group (Fresh Mart)

Position: Manager (Operation)

Duration: From 5th September, 2016 to Present

Responsibilities:

- Improve the operational system, processes and policies in support of organization's mission and vision.
- Product development, Production Process Development, Market Development.
- Monitor costs, expenses and manage budget for the local branch.

02. Gemcon Food and Agricultural Products Ltd. (Meena Bazar)

Position: Manager, Outlet

Duration: From 10th August 2015 to 04th September 2016

Responsibilities:

- Managing & motivating a team to increase sales and ensure efficiency.
- Managing stock levels and making key decisions about stock control, protecting stock loss & wastage.
- Analyzing sales figures and forecasting future sales of the outlet and product wise.

03. Pran-Rfl Group (Best Buy)

Position: Manager, Outlet

Duration: From 1th October, 2013 to 07th August, 2015

Responsibilities:

- Formulating and executing sales plans as well as customer service.
- To monitor and supervise the outlet operation activities.
- Ensuring compliance with all outlet policies & procedure.

04. Brac Aarong

Position: Sales Associate

Duration: From 10st August, 2009 to 30th September, 2013

Responsibilities:

- Customer service & assisting the customer.
- P.O.S & cash handling.
- Handling the CRM.
- Card machine handling & upload.

05. Kay Craft

Position: Sales Associate

Duration: From 1st January, 2009 to 30th July, 2009

Responsibilities:

- Customer service & assisting the customer.
- Maintain proper product display.
- A team work for total sale increase.
- Post- Graduate Diploma in Supply Chain Management (PGDSCM), Bangladesh Institute Of Management Studies (BiMS) (Running)
- Post- Graduate Diploma in Industrial Management (PGDIM), Bangladesh Institute Of Management (BIM) (Running)
- M.S.S. (Master's) in Economics, National University, 2nd Class, 2013.
- B.S.S. (Hon's) in Economics, National University, 2nd Class, 2012
- H.S.C in **Humanities**, **Salimabad Moha Biddaloy**, 3.20 out of 5, 2008.
- S.S.C in **Humanities**, **Daibajnahati B.M High School**, 3.38 out of 5,
- Certificate course on Export & Import in Bangladesh at bdjobs Training.
- Certificate course on Global Supply Chain Management at bdjobs Training.
- Selling Skill For Success at Aim Plus.

TRAINING & CERTIFICATION

EDUCATION

REFERENCES

Md. Shamim Hawladar

Sr. Traffic Officer

Mongla Port Authority

Mongla, Bagerhat

Mobile: +88017 14 597 605

Mehran Rahman Khan

Director Of Company

Paragon Group

Paragon House, 5 Mohakhali, C/A,

Dhaka-1212.

Mobile: +88017 11 526 219

DECLARATION

"I certify that all information stated in this resume is true and complete to the best of my knowledge"

SIGNATURE

K. Dero RF

(Md. AbuSaleh Musa Khan)